<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[sheynk]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[sheynk]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 19:02:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>In my estimation, for a carmaker that is still only delivering one car model in any semi-significant volume, Tesla takes up far more of the conversation about EVs than is reasonable. Make a reservation now for the seven-passenger Model X, and you might — might — still get your all-electric SUV in 2016. (Tesla’s record for shipping in a timely manner is exceedingly poor.) My colleague Chris Ziegler was impressed when he got an early drive, and I have a pretty favorable idea of what to expect, as it uses the same basic platform and engine as the excellent Model S. But potentially more relevant will be the Model 3, a smaller, less expensive sedan that will compete with the likes of the BMW 3 Series. (Though in truth, Tesla says the Model 3 should start around $35,000, while a BMW 340i I recently tested came in at a whopping $57,000. So BMW might be pricing itself out of the "less expensive" market.) Elon Musk says the car will be shown in March. No matter how many Teslas ultimately roll off the line in 2016, the company continues to push other major OEMs like Porsche, which green-lit the Mission E concept precisely because of the Model S’s success.</p>]]></description>
            <link>undefinedin-my-estimation-for-a-carmaker-that-is-still-only-deliveri/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">db2a04f7-476a-414e-9560-47d3389c65dd</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 19:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>